

CANDIDATE ASSESSMENT REPORT

For: Dr. JOY

Re: Senior Java Developer

Mr Pham Quang Minh

Navigos Search's Assessment

Qualifications and Experience

- Graduated from FPT University, major in Software Engineering
- About 04 years experience as Java Developer at FPT Software

Critical Skills

- Basic English (better and read and write)
- Programming: Java, Android, C/C++, C#, .Net, HTML.
- Database: SQLite, SQLServer, MySQL
- Server: Azure, AWS
- Framework: Java Spring...

Motivation

• He wants to find a new opportunity to further develop his career.

Income

- Current salary: averagely 18.5 Million VND (Net)
- Expected salary: 25 Million VND (Net)

Availability

To be discussed upon confirmation of offer

Prepared by: NGUYEN NGOC UYEN Recruitment Consultant

23/09/2020

The assessment report is a subjective evaluation of the candidate based on facts as validated through CV screening, interviews & skill assessment.

Reference check will be conducted upon shortlist for offer.

Ho Chi Minh Office



RESUME OF THE CANDIDATE

Personal Information		
Full name	PHAM QUANG MINH	
Gender	Male	
Date of birth	Jun 28, 1993	13
Address	Trieu Khuc, Thanh Xuan, Ha Noi	

Career Summary		
Jun 2016 – Present Oct 2016 - Present Jun 2016 - Oct 2016	FPT SOFTWARE Java Developer C/C++ Developer	
May 2016 - Aug 2016	FPT UNIVERSITY Capstone Project	
Oct 2015 - Jan 2016	THIENVIETIT Android Developer	
May 2015 - Sep 2015 Jun 2015 - Sep 2015 May 2015 - Jun 2015	FPT SOFTWARE COBOL Developer Tester	

Work Experience & Qualification In Details

OBJECTIVE

Seeking position of a Back-end Developer where I would be able to put to use the knowledge gained in the software development cycle and technical aptitude.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2016 – Present FPT SOFTWARE
Apr 2020 - Present Java Developer

- Create detail design and create API with java and restful services.
- Read SRS design documentation for system requirements.
- Create Unit Test.
- · Review detail design and review source code.

Aug 2017 - Mar 2020 Java Developer



- Create service for UI or convert package.
- Communicate with client for requirements through onsite.
- · Deploy application on cloud server.
- Fix bug and optimize code.

Oct 2016 - Jul 2017

Java Developer

- Create detail design and API with Java Spring and MyBatis, MySql, Amazon Service.
- Read basic design and confirm to create code for accordance with requirements.
- Communicate with client for requirements through onsite.
- Create and execute project work plans and revises as appropriate to meet changing needs and requirements.
- Fix bug and optimize code

Jun 2016 - Oct 2016

C/C++ Developer

- Maintain, migrate one of Japan Government Systems.
- Create design and code tool to migrate.
- Communicate with client for requirements through onsite.
- Create and execute project work plans and revises as appropriate to meet changing needs and requirements.

May 2016 - Aug 2016

FPT UNIVERSITY

Capstone Project

- Team leader of capstone project team.
- Give an idea about project, execute project plan, divide the work for member and coding.
- Write detail design and system architectural design.

Oct 2015 - Jan 2016

THIENVIETIT

Android Developer

- Develop a application on mobile for website nhandantv.vn
- Self-learning technology and communicate with customer for requirements.

May 2015 - Sep 2015

Jun 2015 - Sep 2015

FPT SOFTWARE

COBOL Developer

- Maintain a management software for enterprises.
- Review design pattern and source code after running migrate tool.

May 2015 - Jun 2015

Tester

- Testing for a software is used to share ideas in a meeting.
- Implement test case and log bug for onsite.

PROJECTS

Fsoft Project

(Apr 2020 - Present)

Customer	Vietnamese Customer
Description	Create new modules in a application or create new admin website.
Team size	10
My position	Back-end Developer



My responsibilities	Lead a team create detail designCreate Unit TestReview detail design and review source code
Technologies used	Java Spring Framework, JDK1.8.0, Git, Microsoft Word and Excel, IntelliJ Idea, MariaDB, Visual Paradigm, Heidi SQL, Postman, Swagger

Toolbox Project

(Aug 2017 - Mar 2020)

Customer	American Customer
Description	Create service to manage aircraft data, convert data to serve the production process.
Team size	17
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Develope - Optimize code - Fix bug
Technologies used	Spring Tool Suite, SQLServer, Java Spring Framework, JDK1.8.0, Azure, AWS, Putty, Fire Zilla, Git, Elasticsearch, ActiveMQ, Tomcat 8, VPN

E-learning Project

(Oct 2016 - Jul 2017)

Customer	Japanese Customer
Description	- Create new system to replace the old system to manage tutorial centers of Japan.
Team size	50
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	DevelopCreate API for clientOptimize codeFix bug and team lead javadoc
Technologies used	Eclipse, MySQL, Java Spring, JDK1.7, MyBatis, Firefox 48.0, add on RestClient

Management Of Civil Status Project

(Jun 2016 - Oct 2016)

Customer	Japanese Customer



	- Maintain and migrate source code of Management Of Civil Status system.
Description	
Team size	30
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Maintain and create tool is used to migrate.
Technologies used	Visual Studio 2012, Excel 2013

NhandanTV Application Project

(Oct 2015 - Jan 2016)

Customer	NhandanTV Customer
Description	- Create application mobile for website nhandantv.vn
Team size	2
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Develop android application
Technologies used	Android Studio, JDK1.7

NDN2 Project

(Jun 2015 - Sep 2015)

Customer	Japanese Customer
Description	- Maintain and migrate a management software for enterprises.
Team size	12
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Maintain and review source code converted from PLI to COBOL.
Technologies used	PLI and COBOL programming

Team Idea Sharing Project

(May 2015 - Jun 2015)

Customer	Japanese Customer
Description	- Testing for a software is used to share ideas in a meeting.
Team size	4
My position	Tester
My responsibilities	Test software and log bug for onsite
Technologies used	Excel 2013

Weight Control Project



(May 2016 - Aug 2016)

Customer	Capstone Project
	- An application that helps control weight and help your health gets better.
Description	
Team size	5
My position	Developer, Leader
	Team leader of capstone project team.
	Give an idea about project, execute project plan, divide the work for member
My responsibilities	and coding.
	Write detail design and system architectural design.
	- Android Studio
	- SQLite
Technologies used	- Arduino embedded
	- Excel 2013, Word 2013

Education and Professional Development

ACADEMIC EDUCATION Oct 2011 - Aug 2016

FPT University

Major: Software Engineer

SKILLS

• Language: English - Upper Intermediate

• Programming: Java, Android, C/C++, C#, .Net, HTML.

• Database: SQLite, SQLServer, MySQL

Server: Azure, AWS.